question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "The Killer Whale is considered a type of dolphin.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We "
                 "Can&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tinting&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Popup fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharaoh from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pardonable is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion "
                 "in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Devilled.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]

